foreign
[Music]
I spend a lot of time alone I've been
this way since I was a child I wanted to
be many things when I grew up and one of
them was a biologist because I enjoyed
spending time out in nature observing
the wild world
what I didn't know was that no matter
where life took me I could still live
that dream in my own small way nearly
each day whether permitting I go out
with my dog Iger and spend time waiting
and watching for the beauty hidden in
plain sight
[Music]
foreign
I never feel so whole and so surrounded
by life and connection as I do when I'm
out in nature
when I think of friendship I think of
the creatures that coexist in my world
my favorite Willow and oak tree that I
planted by my home
these are friends though not in your
typical way
[Music]
I've always sustained unconventional
friendships and to be honest I never
thought this was odd until I got older
and felt obligated to fit in I made a
video a couple months ago about how I
struggled to make human friends for a
long time it took a while to get older
and slowly build lasting friendships
with lovely Kindred Spirits but I'll
never be someone with a large amount of
relationships in my life at least not
human ones
[Music]
I remember a teacher once called me a
Hermit for wanting to sit in a quiet
place instead of going to recess she
took away my book and told me to act
normal I do think that in this day and
age when we're so connected with each
other than ever we forget that it is
completely normal and okay to not have
an amazing exciting bustling life or
social life for that matter perhaps we
should take time to understand and
accept who we are our true nature and
find Value in the amount of energy we
have even if it falls short of what we
think we'd like to be
I never felt so at peace until I really
listened and I hope you follow where
that inner truth takes you whether you
are a very social person or not so much
and find ways to give and to support
others in your own unique way
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
I found several leaves and some pieces
of bark and lichen at the lake today and
so I took them home to kind of take a
closer look and study them under my
magnifying glass and make a amateur
attempt to categorize them and write
down my observations and it's so much
fun I feel like even though I did not
pursue a career in the Life Sciences I
can still have fun and really enjoy
learning about that aspect of life at
the end of the day my more artistic
sensibilities took over and pushed me in
a different direction but I do think it
is so important to really consider those
unlived lives and find ways to
incorporate aspects of that into your
daily life I think it makes a life
experience so much richer this is a
short but hopefully sweet video this
week I had quite a few things going on
and so going out to the lake and having
a quiet day creating art and all that
was so special to me and it inspired
kind of revisiting that theme of
friendships I was so moved and initially
surprised by how many people related to
the video and have felt how I have felt
when I was younger and it was a very
very moving it was so lovely to have
conversations with people and open that
conversation of what does it mean to
have close friendships is something
wrong with me if I'm not a super social
person I also place a lot of value and
connection and friendship with things
that are not particularly human in
origin I also value time in nature
because I find it to be a really
self-reflective environment where I can
become more of my own friend there are
several people in my life and my family
as well that are so close to me and
represent such important bonds of
kindred spirit and I really value those
people to find Spirits you really
connect with and I am also feel very
very lucky that I have that in my
husband as well sending so much love to
all of you thank you for all your
kindness and your support and I will see
you soon
[Music]